i have been studying doterra's
compensation plan for the last couple of
weeks
and i have been told that it's super
easy
if you just keep at it to earn 32 000
per month all you have to do is have
three friends sign up through friends
who sign up three friends right the
power of three
so what that looks like is simply having
three friends who
want to also make thirty two thousand
dollars a month eventually
who are passionate about essential oils
and getting the message out there
all of those what those three friends
just have to do is sign up three friends
each get bringing us to nine people
each of those nine sign up three friends
bringing us to 27 people
who sign up three friends bringing us to
81 who signed up three friends bringing
us to 243.
it was hard to fit the people in so i
just made little dots it's a nine by
nine square equaling 81.
um my hand got tired so they're bigger
and then they get smaller so i'm sorry
that you can't see that and then i just
switched to making each one of these
squares so each one of those 81 people
each sign up three bringing us to 729
for each sign up three so we have a
three by three
meta square of the of nine of these
right
so we're at 2187 people for a total of 3
280 people now that can seem daunting
but if you just keep at it you will
eventually get to 32
000 a month after all there are
7.6 billion people on this planet
right what's 3 000 in
7.6 billion right now doterra is one
of the leading sales companies for
essential oils
they have three million wellness
advocates worldwide
so if you're signing up today you have
three million people you're competing
with
three million people so what would it
take for them to all make it to thirty
two thousand dollars a month
well for those three million to make
nine dollars a month
all they have to do is sign up
9 million right as we go up here
we get to 27 million
okay well this is going gonna take a
while all right so for the three million
to get to the top
means nine million people that they
signed up are making nearly ten thousand
dollars a month
that's pretty awesome i mean i wouldn't
say no to ten thousand dollars a month
there are 27 million people making three
thousand dollars a month i mean that's
still okay
still not you know maybe not enough to
support your family but definitely good
thing as a side hustle
but in order for them to get there they
need these 81 million people to sign up
240 million
7 million sorry 729 million
2 billion 187 million
wow and this
6 billion 561 million
okay um
all of them every single one of them
consuming
and fifty dollars worth of essential
oils per month
right well i don't need a hundred and
fifty dollars of essential oils i would
only do it if i was growing a business
and i knew that i was gonna eventually
get to the 32 000 right i want to invest
in my
in my future my family's future so
these people it would be negative 150
they're earning
and a lot of them are living on less
than a dollar a day so
that line probably isn't there well this
line
needed that line in order to make their
measly nine dollars a month
so they're probably also not buying 150
worth of essential oils
um fifty dollars huh oh
looks like the pyramid just collapsed
because in order
for you to get to 32 000 you have to be
feeding off of
3 000 people's work and commitment
and their passion for essential oils in
order to hope to get to that level
there is not enough room at the top you
have been lied to
every mlm is designed to have this
happen the issue is they tell you
that if you're passionate enough you can
get there there are already three
million other
reps that you are competing with in the
marketplace
please do not shop from mlms do not sign
up for mlms
and stop your friends from doing it
thank you